bidwise.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy - bidwise.com

Bidwise takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy governs and details the main privacy principles we apply to the data we collect through our services.

#### Bidwise services

Bidwise is a specialist in creating personalized advertisements. We work with online partners to build advertisements for their website visitors or prospects and with publishers to display personalized advertisements.

Our aim is to deliver advertisements by displaying products and/or personalized banners that you might be interested in, based on your recent browsing behavior. In particular terms, you visit and browse on Website A and, on a subsequent online visit to Website B, you will see ads personalized by your browsing history on Website A.

With our service, you should receive personalized ads that are more relevant for you than the standard advertising you would receive without Bidwise.

#### Our technology

Bidwise “tags” visitors to its partners' websites with anonymous browser cookies. Users tagged by Bidwise are given an anonymous identifier. At no point does Bidwise collect personal data, such as your name or address.

The browser cookies track the product searches a user has performed on Bidwise partner sites, product interests, and product pages visited.

**What are cookies?** A cookie is a small text file stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. There are two types of cookies:

  * Session cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate on websites. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.

  * Persistent cookies are used to run our technology as they enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our partners' websites. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your internet browser’s ‘help’ file.

Our partners’ advertisements are displayed on many websites: publishers. These publishers may also place cookies on your browser. These cookies are there so that the publishers recognize that Bidwise has a personalized advertisement available for your browser.

#### Data collection and use

We collect anonymous informationWe collect only anonymous data through anonymous cookies that record: events related to your activity on the partner’s website (such as the number of pages viewed, the products you viewed on that website, your searches made on the partner's website)information provided by trusted partners that may include socio-demographic data such as age range, and events related to the Bidwise ad serving activity such as the number of ads displayed to you.

We do know that the internet browser you are using has visited one of our partner sites in the last thirty days.

The cookie information collected aims to increase the relevancy of the ads being displayed to you.

The data we collect is also used for reporting purposes, to give our clients and partners more information about the performance of their advertising campaigns, and to improve performance over time.

We do not create segments to specifically target children under 13 years old.

We do not process any information which could be used by Bidwise, directly or indirectly, with the help of a third party or otherwise, to determine the identity of users.

We do not share any information collected with third parties except with our subsidiaries or affiliated companies.

_In compliance with the best industry standards, we use IP addresses for fraud detection purposes (and not for targeting purposes) to help alert us to situations which could not have been caused by human behaviour, such as a massive amount of clicking in a limited period of time._

##### We do not collect any personal information

We do not know who you are. We do not know your address, your place of work, your date of birth, your email address or any other personally identifiable information about you. We do not use or store your IP address for targeting purposes.

We do not collect sensitive information (such as religion, political opinion, health...).

#### Data security and retention

The security of your information is fundamental to Bidwise. We have implemented industry-standard security measures, which include the use of firewalls and encryption.

We retain the anonymous data that we collect for up to 13 months from the date of collection. Our cookies expire 13 months after their last update.

IP addresses are retained for 2 months. In the case of fraud detection, this duration may be extended to 6 months for the purpose of investigation. The IP address is processed by teams separate to those responsible for the Bidwise algorithm.

#### Contact

For any questions on this privacy policy, you can contact: [privacy@Bidwise.com](mailto:privacy@bidwise.com)

#### Changes to our privacy policy

Please note that we may update or change this privacy policy. If we revise our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and to other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any we disclose it. Please check the [Bidwise website](http://www.bidwise.com/privacy) for the latest version of the privacy policy.

Last updated: 12-08-2016
